autoresponseplus.com 2017-06-06

# autoresponder and email marketing software - arpReach

### Your Privacy

We are committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining the security of any personal information received from you. We strictly adhere to the requirements of the data protection legislation in the UK.

We are a registered data user under the Data Protection Act and is registered with the Information Commissioner, as required by law.

The purpose of this statement is to explain to you what personal information we collect and how we may use it.

We do not sell, rent or exchange your personal information with any third party for commercial reasons.

We follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us, to prevent unauthorised access in accordance with UK data protection legislation.

We do not collect sensitive information about you, except when you specifically knowingly provide it. In order to maintain the accuracy of our database, you can check, update or remove your personal details by contacting us.

### Cookies

When you enter our web site we may use cookies. Cookies are small pieces of information which are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive.

These cookies do not store any personal details relating to you. If you do not wish to receive cookies you must not use this web site.

If you have any questions about privacy, please [contact us](https://arpreach.com/contact).

### Information Usage:

### Understanding how we gather information from our visitors and users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you chose to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site(s) or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase.

Like most Web sites, Mutual Advantage Ltd also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit.

Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, thus assisting you insofar that you would not have to re-enter that information each time you visit, or the cookie may control the number of times you are presented a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As Mutual Advantage adopts additional technology, we may also gather information through other means.

In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do make the decision to block our cookies you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences.

### What we do with the information we collect

Like other online publishers and companies, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver a more individual and personalised experience relating to content and advertising. By submitting your information via forms on our website(s) you are signifying your consent that Mutual Advantage may use the contact information you submitted to fulfil and deliver or answer your request for the information or services.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on our sites to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our terms and conditions and privacy policy; services and products offered by us and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by us may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example and our programmers) may access such information.

We also occasionally use third party telephone contact call centres to contact our customers to offer additional services. We will use your information only as permitted by law.

In addition, from time to time as Mutual Advantage grows, we may sell, buy, merge, partner, or joint venture with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets.

We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.
